Slowly.
느리게.
Hold your horses.
당신의 말을 보유.
Why did you save me?
왜 나를 구했습니까?
Why did you follow me in the past three days?
지난 3일 동안 왜 나를 따라왔나요?
Red flowers blossoming in the south.
남쪽에는 붉은 꽃이 핀다.
Miss Chao Nan brought tea.
Chao Nan 씨가 차를 가져왔습니다.
No tea, no wine.
차도, 와인도 없습니다.
And sing the folk songs there.
그리고 그곳에서 민요를 부르세요.
You know who I am now?
지금 내가 누군지 알아요?
I don't know who you are.
나는 당신이 누구인지 모릅니다.
But I know that
하지만 난 그걸 알아요
the organization hasn't forgotten me.
조직은 나를 잊지 않았다.
I'm finally waking up.
나는 마침내 깨어났다.
Is it because
때문인가?
I've been lurking in Shanghai for over a year!
저는 상하이에 1년 넘게 숨어 있었습니다!
Before they awaken me,
그들이 나를 깨우기 전에,
they must observe me secretly
그들은 나를 몰래 관찰해야 해
to check on me
나를 확인하려고
to see if I colluded with the enemy
내가 적과 공모했는지 알아보기 위해
and if my ability
그리고 내 능력이라면
and my ability.
그리고 내 능력.
Right?
오른쪽?
By the way, I have a question.
그런데 질문이 있습니다.
That's the coffee suit just now.
지금 그 커피 정장이군요.
It's closest
가장 가깝습니다
and the most dangerous.
그리고 가장 위험한 것.
Why did you shoot the plaid pants?
체크무늬 바지는 왜 찍은 걸까요?
Newspaper. Newspaper.
신문. 신문.
Selling news.
뉴스를 판매합니다.
The coffee suit
커피 슈트
with the Browning Pistol.
브라우닝 권총으로.
With seven shots,
7개의 샷으로,
the gunshot was slightly stuffy
총소리가 좀 답답했어요
but I heard seven gunshots
하지만 일곱 발의 총소리가 들렸어요
so the pistol
그래서 권총
without bullets
총알 없이
checked pants
체크바지
his hand was a revolver M1917.
그의 손은 M1917 리볼버였습니다.
It has six rounds,
6라운드로 구성되어 있으며,
but he fired three rounds.
하지만 그는 세 발을 발사했습니다.
So his pistol
그래서 그의 권총
with 3 rounds left.
3라운드 남았습니다.
Black top hat.
검은색 모자.
With the Soviet Union's TT33 pistol
소련의 TT33 권총으로
It has eight rounds loaded.
8발의 총알이 장전되어 있습니다.
Loud sound.
소음.
I heard seven gunshots
일곱 발의 총소리가 들렸어요
that means he had one round left
그 말은 그에게 한 라운드 남았다는 뜻이야
I can only save this bullet
이 총알만 아껴둘 수 있어
to checked pants
체크바지에
but if I don't have
하지만 내가 없으면
what if I don't have a magazine?
잡지가 없으면 어떡하지?
I bet you do have a magazine.
아마 잡지를 갖고 계시리라 믿습니다.
You're gambling on your life.
당신은 당신의 인생에 도박을하고 있습니다.
At least I won.
적어도 나는 이겼다.
Alright. Four of clubs.
괜찮은. 4개의 클럽.
Follow the Shanghai traffic line
상하이 교통선을 따라가세요
as instructed by Comrade Sparrow.
참새 동지의 지시에 따라.
You are officially woke up.
당신은 공식적으로 깨어났습니다.
From now on, I'll be your contact.
지금부터 제가 연락드리겠습니다.
You can call me Lao Lu.
저를 라오루라고 부르시면 됩니다.
Old Lu.
올드 루.
Stay here and recover.
여기에 머물면서 회복하세요.
The clinic
클리닉
Is run by my friend from French Concession.
프랑스 조계지 출신의 친구가 운영하고 있습니다.
I woke you up urgently
급하게 당신을 깨웠어요
because our organization received information
우리 조직이 정보를 받았기 때문에
we have a traitor.
배신자가 있습니다.
To be taken to Shanghai.
상하이로 이송됩니다.
Traitor.
배신자.
Who is this traitor?
이 배신자는 누구입니까?
No one knows
아무도 모른다
It's not clear who is escorting him.
누가 그를 호위하고 있는지는 확실하지 않습니다.
According to the specific message,
구체적인 메시지에 따르면,
they will take Train 514 tomorrow
내일 514호 열차를 탈 거예요
from Nanjing to Shanghai.
난징에서 상하이까지.
They'll arrive at the station at about three p.m. tomorrow.
내일 오후 3시쯤에 역에 도착할 거예요.
Zhao An of Taihe Trading Firm
Taihe Trading Firm의 Zhao An
from Taihe Trading Firm.
태허 무역 회사에서.
Zhao An has a secret letter
조안은 비밀편지를 가지고 있다
from a traitor.
배신자에게서.
The traitor will do great harm.
배신자는 큰 해를 끼칠 것입니다.
Many of our comrades who spy in the police station
경찰서를 염탐하는 우리 동지들 중 다수
might be found by him
그 사람이 찾을 수도 있어요
so your mission is
그래서 당신의 임무는
find the traitor
배신자를 찾아라
and eliminate traitors in the organization.
조직의 반역자를 제거합니다.
Yes
예
the difficulties will be great
어려움이 클 것이다
find a way to overcome it.
극복할 수 있는 방법을 찾아보세요.
And look for clues as much as possible.
그리고 최대한 단서를 찾아보세요.
You can deal with it in an emergency.
긴급상황에 대처할 수 있습니다.
At the same time, you should be ready to evacuate.
동시에 대피할 준비도 되어 있어야 합니다.
If your identity is exposed,
본인의 신원이 노출된 경우,
you should leave the firm and Shanghai immediately.
당신은 즉시 회사와 상하이를 떠나야 합니다.
My usual
나의 평소
I promise to complete the task.
나는 그 일을 완수할 것을 약속한다.
The Yumo Calligraphy and Painting Shop on Dongpushi Road.
동푸시로에 있는 유모 서예 및 그림 가게.
This is where we should be contacting later.
나중에 연락해야 할 곳입니다.
This is where we'll be contacting in the future.
앞으로 우리가 연락할 곳은 여기입니다.
Come on, Jiaping.
자, 자핑.
Come on
어서 해봐요
look at this painting.
이 그림을 보세요.
Please write a note for me.
저에게 메모를 써주세요.
Eat while it's hot.
뜨거울 때 먹습니다.
My paintings and your writing
나의 그림과 당신의 글
so a perfect match in Shanghai
그래서 상하이와 완벽하게 일치합니다
no one can find another in Shanghai
상하이에서는 누구도 다른 사람을 찾을 수 없습니다
old Luo,
오래된 루오,
why are you still in the mood for painting?
왜 아직도 그림 그릴 생각이야?
Do you know that Zhao An
자오안(Zhao An)을 아시나요?
zhao An has a meeting today?
자오안이 오늘 회의가 있어요?
Don't blame me for this
이것에 대해 나를 비난하지 마십시오
do you think I'm straightforward?
내가 솔직하다고 생각해?
Now everyone in the business
이제 회사에 있는 모든 사람들이
are saying that you are just a fake brand.
당신은 가짜 브랜드일 뿐이라고 말하고 있습니다.
Zhao An is the real boss of the business.
조안(Zhao An)은 이 사업의 진정한 보스입니다.
That's enough.
충분 해.
But look at this.
하지만 이것 좀 보세요.
The Japanese only call you Zhao An at meetings.
일본인들은 회의에서만 당신을 자오안(Zhao An)이라고 부릅니다.
This is so not fair.
이건 정말 불공평해요.
Jiaping,
자핑,
take a look at the painting for me.
나를 위해 그림을 좀 봐주세요.
Please comment.
의견을 부탁합니다.
Alright.
괜찮은.
And light energy,
그리고 빛 에너지,
contains the power.
힘을 담고 있습니다.
From within.
안으로부터.
Brother,
형제,
It's time to accumulate wealth.
부를 축적할 시간입니다.
You know me.
당신은 나를 알고 있습니다.
Certainly.
틀림없이.
You're my eldest brother, right?
당신은 내 큰 형이군요, 그렇죠?
I'm not like those pushers who
나는 그런 밀어붙이는 사람들과는 다릅니다.
they all went to Zhao An.
그들은 모두 Zhao An으로 갔다.
I'm determined to follow you.
나는 당신을 따르기로 결심했습니다.
Do you think that
당신은 그렇게 생각합니까?
do you think
당신은 생각합니까
I will deal with Zhao An sooner or later?
조만간 자오안과 거래를 하게 될까요?
Not necessarily.
반드시 그런 것은 아닙니다.
I just think
내 생각엔 그냥
If I'm with Zhao An,
내가 조안과 함께라면
wouldn't I be able to use
내가 사용할 수 없을까?
my good handwriting.
내 좋은 손글씨.
You
너
the power of this painting
이 그림의 힘
a bird is out of the wood.
새가 나무에서 나왔습니다.
Write cursive characters in a vigorous and nimble style
활기차고 민첩한 스타일로 필기체 문자를 작성하세요.
also,
또한,
If you open the curtains,
커튼을 열면,
It's bright
밝다
chief Chen
첸 수석
what are you up to?
지금 뭐하고 있어?
I'm sweating.
나는 땀을 흘리고 있어요.
It's too hot to clean up the office.
사무실 청소하기에는 너무 더워요.
Let it out.
그것을 보자.
He's busy.
그는 바쁘다.
I'll get something back.
나는 뭔가를 돌려받을 것이다.
Got to go.
가야.
Based on all information,
모든 정보를 바탕으로,
we can now confirm that
이제 우리는 그것을 확인할 수 있습니다
the traitor Fang Hong Nan was escorted by
배신자 Fang Hong Nan은 호위를 받았습니다.
from Nanjing to Shanghai.
난징에서 상하이까지.
As long as we find the Martial Master and his men
무술가와 그의 부하들을 찾는 한
and find out the traitor's southpaw
그리고 배신자의 왼손잡이를 알아내세요
we can target him and find an opportunity to eliminate traitors.
그를 표적으로 삼아 반역자를 제거할 기회를 찾을 수 있습니다.
But there was an accident.
그런데 사고가 일어났습니다.
Zhao An will take men to guard the train station.
Zhao An은 기차역을 경비하기 위해 사람들을 데려갈 것입니다.
It would cause unpredictable difficulties and dangers
예측할 수 없는 어려움과 위험을 초래할 것입니다.
to the operation.
작업에.
What should I do?
어떻게 해야 하나요?
To go or not?
갈까 말까?
It's too late to report to the organization now.
지금은 조직에 보고하기에는 너무 늦었습니다.
We must make a decision immediately.
우리는 즉시 결정을 내려야 합니다.
Watch your step.
당신의 단계를 시청.
Get out of the way.
비켜가세요.
Please make way.
비켜주세요.
I made some business.
나는 사업을 좀 했어요.
I agreed to meet him at the railway station.
나는 그를 기차역에서 만나기로 약속했습니다.
But Zhao An found out.
하지만 조안(Zhao An)은 그 사실을 알아냈습니다.
The Japanese
일본인
has been very strict recently.
최근에는 매우 엄격해졌습니다.
And Zhao An is the underling of the Japanese.
그리고 자오안은 일본의 부하입니다.
So he used you as his cover.
그래서 그는 당신을 자신의 표지로 이용했습니다.
That's it?
그게 다야?
What about you?
당신은 어때요?
What about me?
나는 어때?
When I asked for your help,
내가 당신에게 도움을 요청했을 때,
you reacted so quickly.
당신은 너무 빨리 반응했습니다.
That there is something
뭔가가 있다는 걸
to hide something on purpose.
일부러 뭔가를 숨기려고요.
Did you also use me to give you a cover?
당신도 나를 이용하여 당신을 보호해 주었나요?
I thought they wanted to catch me.
나는 그들이 나를 붙잡고 싶어한다고 생각했습니다.
Why?
왜?
I participated in an activity
활동에 참여했어요
I participated in an activity against Wang puppet government.
나는 왕 꼭두각시 정부에 반대하는 활동에 참여했습니다.
That's not like you.
그건 당신과는 다릅니다.
When I was a traitor.
내가 배신자였을 때.
By the way,
그런데,
how come I didn't notice
내가 왜 눈치채지 못했지?
your memory is so good.
당신의 기억력은 정말 좋습니다.
When Zhao An caught up with us,
조안이 우리를 따라잡았을 때,
I told you once.
내가 한 번 말했잖아.
Remember all the information
모든 정보를 기억하세요
about the firm,
회사에 대해서,
you're not bad, right?
너 나쁘지 않지, 그렇지?
Exactly the same.
정확히 동일합니다.
I'm the chief of the General Services Section.
저는 총무과장입니다.
But I'm good at that
하지만 난 그게 능숙해
I'm in the accounting office,
저는 회계실에 있어요.
and I'm good at remembering these things.
그리고 저는 이런 것들을 잘 기억해요.
I'm not good at remembering
나는 기억을 잘 못해요
not only these trivial matters.
이런 사소한 문제만이 아니다.
I know.
알아요.
You have a lot of things to ask me.
당신은 나에게 물어볼 것이 많습니다.
Go ahead then.
그럼 계속하세요.
Why you didn't come that day.
그날 왜 안 왔어?
We already investigated.
우리는 이미 조사했습니다.
Luo Guanqun is really something.
Luo Guanqun은 정말 대단합니다.
The so-called Taihe Trading Firm
소위 태화무역회사(Taihe Trading Firm)
the so-called Taihe Firm.
소위 Taihe 회사.
The Imperial Bodyguard
제국 경호원
Is an intelligence station
정보국인가
under the control of Japan's Military Police Headquarters.
일본 헌병 본부의 통제를 받는다.
We can infiltrate our enemies
적에게 침투할 수 있다
we can infiltrate our enemies, right?
우리는 적에게 침투할 수 있지, 그렇지?
That's right.
좋아요.
However,
하지만,
have you thought it over?
생각해 봤어?
Yes, I have.
네, 있어요.
I'm a Party member.
저는 파티원입니다.
I want to do my best
나는 최선을 다하고 싶다
to resist Japan and save the country
일본에 저항하고 나라를 구하려고
and national liberation.
그리고 민족해방.
Once you execute a lurking mission,
숨어있는 미션을 수행하고 나면,
your identity should be more concealed.
당신의 신원은 더 숨겨야합니다.
Please rest assured.
안심하십시오.
I will definitely be able to do it.
나는 확실히 할 수 있을 것이다.
I remember that
나는 그것을 기억한다
to marry Zuo Shuangtao before.
Zuo Shuangtao와 결혼하기 전에.
But you weren't there on the day of the registration.
그런데 당신은 등록 당일 거기에 없었어요.
She must be very sad.
그녀는 매우 슬퍼할 것입니다.
How do you plan to
어떻게 할 계획인가요?
with Zuo Shuangtao?
Zuo Shuangtao와 함께?
I...
나...
I owe her so much.
나는 그녀에게 너무 많은 빚을 지고 있어요.
Pay it back next life.
다음 생에 갚으세요.
Answer me. ??? I fell in love with her. ???
대답 해. ??? 나는 그녀와 사랑에 빠졌습니다. ???
Why didn't you come that day?
그날 왜 안 오셨어요?
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
I thought
나는 생각했다
I can't give you
나는 당신에게 줄 수 없습니다
happy life.
행복한 삶.
So you ran away?
그래서 도망쳤어요?
Come to Shanghai
상하이로 오세요
to be a traitor.
배신자가 되는 것.
I only knew Luo Guanqun by chance.
나는 우연히 Luo Guanqun을 알았습니다.
I didn't know he was working for the Japanese.
나는 그가 일본인을 위해 일하고 있는지 몰랐습니다.
It was too late when I found out.
그걸 알았을 때는 너무 늦었어요.
In addition,
게다가,
just make a living.
그냥 생계를 유지하세요.
You were not like this.
당신은 이렇지 않았습니다.
Yes
예
It was...
그것은 ...
In the past.
과거에.
I was stupid in the past.
나는 과거에 바보였습니다.
Too childish
너무 유치해
and unrealistic.
그리고 비현실적이다.
Including being with me.
나와 함께 있는 것도 포함해서요.
Did you come to Nanjing to find me later?
나중에 나를 찾으러 난징까지 오셨나요?
Bill, please.
빌, 제발요.
Have you finished?
끝났나요?
What about the girl who always comes with you?
항상 당신과 함께 오는 여자는 어떻습니까?
Recently,
최근에,
that girl always came alone
그 여자는 항상 혼자 왔어
and today you're again alone?
그런데 오늘 또 혼자야?
Boss.
사장.
Can you do me a favor?
부탁 하나만 들어줄 수 있나요?
What help?
무슨 도움이 되나요?
That girl of yours
당신의 그 여자
If I come again next time,
다음에 또 온다면,
can the soup be less salty?
수프가 덜 짜게 할 수 있나요?
Use less Kaiyang.
카이양을 적게 사용하세요.
In fact, she doesn't want to trouble you.
사실, 그녀는 당신을 괴롭히고 싶지 않습니다.
She's too shy to say it.
그녀는 너무 부끄러워서 그런 말을 할 수가 없어요.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Please don't tell her.
그녀에게 말하지 마세요.
That I told you this?
내가 너한테 이런 말을 했다고?
Answer me!
대답 해!
Did you come to Nanjing to find me later?
나중에 나를 찾으러 난징까지 오셨나요?
Not really.
설마.
Can I leave now?
지금 떠나도 될까요?
Not yet.
아직 아님.
(Sorry.)
(죄송합니다.)
This drama won't end
이 드라마는 끝나지 않을 거야
the play won't end.
연극은 끝나지 않을 거야.
I accompany you
나는 당신과 동행합니다
I'll go to the Yu Residence with you.
나는 너와 함께 유 레지던스로 갈 것이다.
We need to make them believe
우리는 그들이 믿게 만들어야 해요
that we're couple.
우리가 커플이라고요.
Why should I listen to you?
내가 왜 당신 말을 들어야 합니까?
Go back first
먼저 돌아가세요
pick me up tomorrow morning.
내일 아침에 나를 데리러 오세요.
Let me leave just after taking a shower?
샤워하고 바로 나갈까요?
Where should I go?
난 어디로 가야 해?
To your home.
당신의 집으로.
Wherever you are,
네가 어디에 있든,
where will be my home?
내 집은 어디에 있을까?
I won't go back.
나는 돌아 가지 않을 것이다.
Stop it.
그만해요.
To let your colleagues know about this.
동료들에게 이 사실을 알리기 위해.
Then give me a kiss.
그럼 나에게 키스를 해주세요.
Before I leave.
내가 떠나기 전에.
How annoying.
얼마나 짜증나는지.
You don't want to kiss me?
나한테 키스하고 싶지 않아?
Let me kiss you.
너랑 키스 하고파.
I'm leaving now.
나는 지금 떠난다.
Sir, are you looking for me?
선생님, 저를 찾고 계시나요?
Tonight,
오늘 밤,
bring your people
당신의 사람들을 데려와
to Ci'an Hospital to set up an ambush.
매복을 준비하기 위해 Ci'an 병원으로 이동합니다.
Yes
예
sir, I've heard
선생님, 들었습니다
commander Shanxia is already dead.
Shanxia 사령관은 이미 죽었습니다.
Then what's the purpose of the guard at the hospital?
그렇다면 병원 경비원의 목적은 무엇인가?
I see.
알겠어요.
If the Chinese Communist has surrendered to us,
만약 중국공산당이 우리에게 항복했다면,
Is in the hospital now.
지금은 병원에 있어요.
Have you ever heard of four of clubs?
4개의 클럽에 대해 들어보신 적이 있나요?
Four of clubs
클럽 4개
Is the mole in your firm.
당신 회사의 두더지입니다.
There's a Communist Party of China named Four of Clubs lurking in the background.
배경에는 Four of Clubs라는 중국 공산당이 숨어 있습니다.
Communist Party of China?
중국 공산당?
Who do you think
당신은 누구라고 생각합니까?
of Four Clubs?
4개의 클럽 중?
It's me.
나야.
I see
알겠어요
slowly.
느리게.
Did you hear anything?
무슨 말이라도 들었나요?
What sound?
무슨 소리야?
Don't scare us.
우리를 놀라게하지 마십시오.
The morgue is full of dead bodies.
영안실에는 시체가 가득합니다.
With a dead body in the morgue?
영안실에 시체가 있나요?
I really heard that.
정말 그런 말을 들었습니다.
You must have misheard it.
당신은 그것을 잘못 들었음에 틀림없다.
Come on. Let's go.
어서 해봐요. 갑시다.
Little Liu.
리틀 리우.
The patient at bed 307 passed away.
307호 병상에 있던 환자가 사망했습니다.
Bring her to the morgue.
그녀를 영안실로 데려가세요.
Alright.
괜찮은.
What the hell!
도대체 무슨 일이야!
Can't we even sleep now?
우리 이제 잠도 못 자?
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Don't move.
움직이지 마세요.
What's up
무슨 일이야
she is the number 11.
그녀는 11번이에요.
You remember that I put it in.
넣었던 기억나시죠?
Didn't you remember it?
기억하지 못하셨나요?
Maybe I forgot.
어쩌면 내가 잊어버렸나 보다.
It must have slipped my mind.
내 마음이 미끄러 졌나 봐요.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
You know what?
그거 알아?
I'm the most
나는 가장
most meticulous person.
가장 세심한 사람.
To plug in all the plugs in.
모든 플러그를 꽂으려면.
Then tell me
그럼 말 해주세요
why was the latch on the morgue cabinet
왜 영안실 캐비닛에 걸쇠가 있었나요?
Is open?
열려 있나요?
It's scary.
무서워.
Yes, it is.
예, 그렇습니다.
Bring me to the morgue.
나를 영안실로 데려가세요.
Who are you?
누구세요?
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 오십시오.
The traitor Fang Hong Nan has arrived in Shanghai.
배신자 Fang Hong Nan이 상하이에 도착했습니다.
Why is he suddenly so quiet?
그 사람 갑자기 왜 이렇게 조용해?
Such an important person
이렇게 중요한 사람이구나
could've caused huge waves.
엄청난 파장을 일으켰을 수도 있습니다.
But they don't show any sign to take any action.
그러나 그들은 어떤 조치를 취하겠다는 어떤 조짐도 보이지 않습니다.
Could she be
그녀는 그럴 수 있을까
when Shanxia was assassinated at the railway station,
Shanxia가 기차역에서 암살당했을 때,
fang Hongnan was also injured.
Fang Hongnan도 부상을 입었습니다.
I heard that the guards under the mountain were injured.
산 아래 경비병들이 다쳤다는 소식을 들었습니다.
To hide his identity,
자신의 정체를 숨기기 위해,
and framed Fang Hongnan as a guard?
Fang Hongnan을 경비원으로 모함 했나요?
Among the injured victims who checked in today,
오늘 확인된 부상자 중에는
Is still no left-handed.
아직은 왼손잡이가 아닙니다.
Would it be that Fang Hongnan was seriously injured and died?
Fang Hongnan이 심각한 부상을 입고 사망했을까요?
Try to think again.
다시 생각해 보세요.
Try to think about it.
그것에 대해 생각해보십시오.
Anything abnormal tonight?
오늘 밤 뭔가 이상한 일이라도 있나요?
Hearing your words,
당신의 말을 듣고,
I remember that.
나는 그것을 기억한다.
I saw the back of a male doctor.
나는 남자 의사의 뒷모습을 보았다.
But the doctors on duty tonight
하지만 오늘 밤 근무중인 의사들은
on duty tonight
오늘 밤 근무중
but there are no male doctors.
그런데 남자 의사는 없어요.
That man
그 사람
Is pretending to be the male doctor.
남자 의사인 척 하고 있어요.
Stand up.
일어서세요.
That's the way I saw his back.
나는 그의 뒷모습을 그렇게 보았다.
He must want to run away.
그 사람은 도망가고 싶은 게 틀림없어요.
But he fell to his death.
그러나 그는 쓰러져 죽었습니다.
Let's see who she is.
그녀가 누구인지 봅시다.
Aren't these the bodies in Counter No.2?
이거 2번 카운터에 있던 시체 아닌가요?
Let's see who it is
누구인지 볼까요
section Chief Chen, Miss Zuo
섹션 수석 Chen, Miss Zuo
get in the car
차에 타라
old Luo asked you to come?
루오 늙은이가 오라고 했나?
It's not like you don't know
당신이 모르는 것과는 다릅니다
you know that.
당신은 그것을 알고 있습니다.
When I heard that Ms. Zuo is the niece of the Yu family,
Zuo 씨가 Yu 가문의 조카라는 소식을 들었을 때,
when you hear that Miss Zuo is the niece.
Miss Zuo가 조카라는 말을 들었을 때.
Forget about it.
잊어버리세요.
We still have to do some shopping in the mall.
우리는 아직 쇼핑몰에서 쇼핑을 좀 해야 해요.
No need.
필요 없음.
They've got all the gifts.
그들은 모든 선물을 가지고 있습니다.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
It's very considerate of me.
그것은 나를 매우 배려합니다.
Shuangtao, it's really you.
Shuangtao, 정말 당신이에요.
Look at this.
이거 봐요.
You've changed so much.
당신은 너무 많이 변했습니다.
Come on, aunt.
어서, 이모.
We haven't seen each other for years.
우리는 몇 년 동안 서로를 보지 못했습니다.
You look younger every day.
당신은 매일 더 젊어 보입니다.
Not really.
설마.
I'm already old.
나는 이미 늙었다.
Mrs. Yu doesn't know she's not aged.
Yu 부인은 자신이 늙지 않았다는 것을 모릅니다.
She should be in her early thirties at most.
그녀는 기껏해야 30대 초반이어야 한다.
He's a man of striking appearance.
그는 눈에 띄는 외모를 가진 사람이다.
Such a sweet young man like him.
그와 같은 사랑스러운 청년.
Yes
예
jiaping,
자핑,
you mentioned it in the letter.
당신은 편지에서 그것을 언급했습니다.
Hi, Mrs. Yu.
안녕하세요, 유씨.
So you're Jia Ping?
그럼 당신이 Jia Ping인가요?
You finally see your natural face today.
오늘 드디어 자연스러운 얼굴을 보셨군요.
Go there.
저기로가.
Every letter of Shuangtao mentions you.
Shuangtao의 모든 편지에는 당신이 언급되어 있습니다.
But in recent years,
그러나 최근 몇 년 동안,
he didn't mention it much this year.
그는 올해 그것에 대해 많이 언급하지 않았습니다.
I thought...
나는 생각했다 ...
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
Look at my mouth.
내 입을 좀 봐.
Oh, right.
아, 그렇죠.
Why did you come to Shanghai
상하이에 왜 오셨나요?
without telling me?
나한테 말하지 않고?
I wrote you a letter.
나는 당신에게 편지를 썼습니다.
You didn't receive it?
받지 못하셨나요?
No, I didn't.
아니요, 그렇지 않았습니다.
A month ago.
한 달 전.
It's alright.
괜찮아.
We're all here now.
우리는 이제 모두 여기에 있습니다.
This is the most important thing.
이것이 가장 중요한 것입니다.
It doesn't matter if I receive this letter.
내가 이 편지를 받아도 상관없어요.
In this age,
이 시대에는
everything is in chaos.
모든 것이 혼란에 빠졌습니다.
It became a mess.
엉망이되었습니다.
And got lost.
그리고 길을 잃었습니다.
They are normal.
그들은 정상입니다.
Normal.
정상.
Standing here and talking for so long,
여기 서서 오랫동안 이야기를 나누다 보면
go in and talk.
들어가서 얘기해 보세요.
Go in.
들어가세요.
Mrs. Yu, I won't go in there.
유씨, 저는 거기 안 들어갑니다.
I've completed my task
나는 내 임무를 완수했다
that's it.
그게 다야.
Thank you for your hard work.
여러분의 노고에 감사드립니다.
Goodbye, Mrs. Yu.
안녕히 계세요, 유씨.
-Bye. -See you.
-안녕. -또 봐요.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 오십시오.
You have become
당신은
have become more beautiful.
더욱 아름다워졌습니다.
What?
무엇?
Drive slowly.
천천히 운전하다.
Is this Jiaping?
여기가 자핑인가요?
You don't know.
당신은 모른다.
Our Zheng family was once
우리 Zheng 가족은 한때
we were all from wealthy families.
우리는 모두 부유한 집안 출신이었습니다.
Within tens of miles,
수십 마일 이내,
within a radius.
반경 내.
Guoguo once mentioned this before.
Guoguo는 이전에 이것을 언급한 적이 있습니다.
My mother told me that
우리 엄마가 나한테 그러셨어
she was thin and weak as a child
그녀는 어렸을 때부터 마르고 약했다
and was bullied a lot.
그리고 왕따도 많이 당했어요.
And you protected her.
그리고 당신은 그녀를 보호했습니다.
So many brothers and sisters.
형제자매가 너무 많아요.
Your mom and I are the closest.
너희 엄마와 나는 가장 가깝다.
Don't mention it.
그것을 언급하지 마십시오.
Whenever I mention your mother,
내가 네 어머니를 언급할 때마다,
whenever I mention your mom.
내가 네 엄마를 언급할 때마다.
Guoguo, now that you're in Shanghai
궈궈, 이제 상하이에 왔으니
you're here,
너 여기 있네,
my aunt's house is your home.
우리 이모 집이 네 집이야.
You can live here.
여기서 살 수 있습니다.
You can tell her whatever she needs
그녀에게 필요한 것은 무엇이든 말해도 됩니다.
you always told her
당신은 항상 그녀에게 말했어요
to take it easy.
편하게 지내려고.
Do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
by the way, there's work.
그건 그렇고, 일이 있어요.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
And don't worry.
그리고 걱정하지 마세요.
I'll tell your uncle
내가 네 삼촌한테 말해줄게
and ask him to
그리고 그에게 부탁해
and take care of it.
그리고 그것을 처리하십시오.
Search carefully.
신중하게 검색하세요.
Must be happy
행복해야 해
with your husband.
너의 남편과 함께.
It's getting late.
늦겠다.
I have to prepare lunch.
점심을 준비해야 해요.
I'll cook a few dishes
내가 몇 가지 요리를 해줄게
to welcome you.
당신을 환영합니다.
Mrs. Yu is beautiful and kind.
유씨는 아름답고 친절해요.
You can cook too.
요리도 할 수 있어요.
It's great honor
대단한 영광이네요
to marry you.
당신과 결혼하기 위해.
Guoguo.
궈궈.
A handsome man like Jiaping
자핑처럼 잘생긴 남자
young people like him
그 사람을 좋아하는 젊은이들
should have been brought to your aunt long ago.
오래 전에 이모님께 데려왔어야 했는데.
You guys chat.
여러분, 채팅하세요.
You guys have a chat.
여러분, 채팅을 해보세요.
Xiaoli, come with me.
샤오리, 나와 함께 가자.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Mrs. Yu mentioned the letter just now.
방금 유씨가 그 편지에 대해 언급했어요.
Big Scoop is suspecting.
Big Scoop이 의심하고 있습니다.
What can we do
우리는 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
how about this?
이건 어때?
You can write more letters
더 많은 편지를 쓸 수 있어요
within one year.
1년 이내.
And different periods.
그리고 다른 기간.
Using papers from different periods
다양한 시대의 논문을 활용
and pens.
그리고 펜.
I can leave the postmark
소인을 남겨둘 수 있어요
I will find a way.
나는 방법을 찾을 것이다.
I'm going to work in the business.
나는 사업에 종사할 예정이다.
You're so meticulous.
당신은 정말 꼼꼼해요.
To be a traitor.
배신자가 되려면.
What a pity
정말 안타깝네요
chief Chen
첸 수석
what took you so long?
왜 그렇게 늦었 어?
For you to come.
당신을 위해.
Waiting for me?
나를 기다려 줘?
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
By order of Chief Kimura,
기무라 소장의 명령에 따라
all employees of the firm
회사의 모든 직원
to the grove behind the building.
건물 뒤 숲으로.
I don't know
모르겠습니다
I don't know either
나도 모르겠어요
It's very likely that
그럴 가능성이 매우 높다
nothing good.
좋은 건 없어.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
This is the horse Zhao An gave to Mucun.
이것은 조안이 무춘에게 준 말이다.
It was said to be transported from Manchuria.
만주에서 운반되었다고 합니다.
From Central Asia.
중앙아시아 출신.
Look at that.
저것 봐.
What does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
You asked us here to watch others hang?
다른 사람들이 매달리는 것을 지켜보라고 우리에게 요청하셨나요?
I'm afraid we're not watching others being hanged,
다른 사람들이 교수형당하는 모습을 우리가 보고 있지 않아서 유감입니다.
rather, one of us will be hanged!
오히려 우리 중 한 명이 교수형을 당할 것입니다!
Have you heard who is going to be hanged?
누가 교수형을 당할지 들어보셨나요?
No one.
아무도.
Is everyone here?
모두 여기 있나요?
Everyone is here.
모두가 여기에 있습니다.
Everyone,
모든 사람,
although Taihe Trading Firm
비록 태허무역회사
Is a trading company,
무역회사이며,
you know who we work for
우리가 누구 밑에서 일하는지 아시죠?
what we do
우리가 하는 일
we all know that
우리 모두는 그것을 알고 있습니다
that some anti-Japanese elements
일부 반일적 요소가
tried to sneak in
몰래 들어가려고 했어
to steal intelligence
지능을 훔치려고
and sabotage the China-Japan friendship,
중일우호를 파괴하고,
to bring common prosperity to East Asia.
동아시아 공동번영을 실현하겠습니다.
Today
오늘
we gathered here
우리는 여기에 모였다
because we have definite information.
확실한 정보가 있기 때문이죠.
There's a spy
스파이가 있어요
In the firm
회사에서
under the cover of four of clubs.
4개 클럽의 표지 아래.
Today
오늘
we're going to show a ghost
우리는 유령을 보여주려고 해요
kill the four of clubs.
클럽 네 개를 죽여라.
I'm afraid you don't know
당신이 모르실까 봐 걱정이에요
under threat from
로부터 위협을 받고 있다
by the Great Japanese Empire and the peaceful government,
대일제국과 평화정부에 의해,
a CPC defector came here
중국공산당 탈북자가 여기 왔다
he identified four of clubs.
그는 4개의 클럽을 식별했습니다.
Officer Mu Cun,
무춘(Mu Cun) 경관,
now show us the traitor.
이제 배신자를 보여주세요.
Come on out!
나오세요!
Fang Hongnan,
팡홍난,
all the people in the commercial are here.
광고에 나오는 사람들이 다 여기 있어요.
Everyone in the business is here.
사업에 종사하는 모든 사람이 여기에 있습니다.
You have to make sure
꼭 확인하셔야 해요
look at them.
저들을 봐.
Check out
확인해 보세요
see if there are any Chinese Communists.
중국 공산주의자가 있는지 살펴보세요.
Chief Kimura.
기무라 과장.
I need to confirm one by one.
하나씩 확인을 해봐야겠습니다.
How about this?
이건 어때?
If he's not someone,
그 사람이 아니라면,
I'll pat his shoulder.
나는 그의 어깨를 두드려줄 것이다.
The sleeve and button of his left hand
왼손의 소매와 단추
Is much worse than that of his right hand
오른손보다 훨씬 심해요
It shows that he wrote with his left hand.
왼손으로 글을 썼다는 것을 알 수 있습니다.
It's the same as my previous judgment.
제가 예전에 판단한 것과 똑같습니다.
Is that Fang Hongnan?
팡홍난인가요?
This person?
이 사람?
I am an unmarried accountant.
저는 미혼 회계사입니다.
I'm sure you've never seen me before.
나는 당신이 전에 나를 본 적이 없다고 확신합니다.
I'm Luo Guanqun's.
저는 Luo Guanqun의 사람입니다.
I'm the manager's wife.
저는 매니저의 아내입니다.
How could it be me?
어떻게 나일 수 있니?
Alright.
괜찮은.
Kimura must be looking for
키무라가 찾고 있을 거야
the secret letter under the mountain.
산 밑의 비밀편지.
If he gets the secret letter first,
그 사람이 비밀편지를 먼저 받으면,
It would be over.
끝났을 것입니다.
But there was no letter on the body in the hospital.
하지만 병원의 시체에는 편지가 없었습니다.
Instead of just sitting here,
여기 그냥 앉아 있는 것보다
you'd better go to the commercial firm and investigate
상업 회사에 가서 조사해 보는 게 좋을 거야
Mr. Fang,
팡 씨,
I am just a guard.
나는 단지 경비원일 뿐이다.
Sir, there's no one in the business.
선생님, 회사에 사람이 없어요.
I'm going to the door.
나는 문으로 갈 것이다.
Mr. Fang,
팡 씨,
look carefully.
주의 깊게 봐.
Don't get the wrong person.
사람을 잘못 만나지 마세요.
You would be four of clubs.
당신은 4개의 클럽이 될 것입니다.
I once saw you
나는 당신을 한 번 본 적이 있습니다
a Communist Party meeting.
공산당 회의.
Fang Hongnan.
팡홍난.
Are you sure that
확실합니까?
chen Jiaping is four of clubs.
Chen Jiaping은 4개의 클럽입니다.
No, no, Captain Zhao.
아뇨, 아뇨, 자오 선장님.
Mr. Fang must have got the wrong person.
Fang 씨가 사람을 잘못 보셨나 봐요.
Manager Luo.
루오 매니저.
Officer Kimura,
기무라 장교,
I've been working in the business for a long time.
나는 오랫동안 사업에 종사해 왔습니다.
I can't be a Communist Party spy.
나는 공산당 스파이가 될 수 없습니다.
Mr. Luo can testify for me.
Luo 씨가 저를 위해 증언해 드릴 수 있습니다.
Officer Kimura.
기무라 장교.
Even if I was a Communist Party spy,
내가 공산당 간첩이었어도
I wouldn't choose a four of clubs
나는 4개의 클럽을 선택하지 않을 것이다
to be my code name.
내 코드네임이 되도록.
With my personality,
내 성격으로는,
why should I choose Q or K?
왜 Q나 K를 선택해야 하나요?
Chen Jiaping,
첸 지아핑(Chen Jiaping),
no need to deny it.
그것을 부정할 필요는 없습니다.
I want to invite you
당신을 초대하고 싶습니다
to test my horse.
내 말을 시험하려고.
To
에게
to think.
생각하다.
Hello
안녕하세요
I want to see Chen Jiaping.
천자핑(Chen Jiaping)을 보고 싶습니다.
I... I know you are
난... 당신이 그런 줄 알아요
you're the girlfriend of Chief Chen
당신은 첸 서장의 여자친구예요
she's called
그녀는 전화했다
left Pair Tao.
페어타오를 떠났다.
That's right
좋아요
miss Zuo, are you here to see Section Chief Chen?
주오 씨, 첸 과장을 만나러 오셨나요?
You came at a bad time
당신은 나쁜 시간에 왔어
what's up
무슨 일이야
today,
오늘,
with the firm today.
오늘 회사랑.
Or is it something
아니면 뭔가인가?
chief Chen is in trouble
첸 팀장은 고민에 빠졌다
what happened to Jiaping?
자핑에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
I just want to
나는 그저 원할 뿐이야
I couldn't bear to watch it anymore.
나는 더 이상 그것을 지켜볼 수 없었다.
So I ran back.
그래서 나는 다시 달려갔다.
I advise you
당신에게 충고합니다
go back now.
지금 돌아가세요.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Can you take me to see him?
나를 데리고 그를 만나러 갈 수 있나요?
If you
만약 너라면
the place,
장소,
let me show you.
보여드리죠.
Hurry.
서두르다.
Guoguo.
궈궈.
Jia Ping.
지아핑.
Jiaping.
가평.
Miss Zuo, you are here.
Miss Zuo, 당신은 여기 있습니다.
You two...
너희 둘...
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Miss Zuo.
미스 주오.
You were also kept in the dark like us?
당신도 우리처럼 어둠 속에 갇혀 있었나요?
Your boyfriend, Chen Jia Ping
당신의 남자 친구 Chen Jia Ping
Is a Communist.
공산주의자입니다.
That's impossible.
그것은 불가능합니다.
That's bullshit!
그건 헛소리야!